<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/wooriapt.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/wooriapt.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-07-08T14:33:55+00:00</updated><id>/wooriapt.github.io/</id><title type="html">CUBE ON_PaRK</title><subtitle>BlockChain Developer from Somewhere</subtitle><entry><title type="html">CUBE ON Token Sale Agreement_2</title><link href="/wooriapt.github.io/Purchase-Agreement_2/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="CUBE ON Token Sale Agreement_2" /><published>2018-07-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-07-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/wooriapt.github.io/Purchase%20Agreement_2</id><content type="html" xml:base="/wooriapt.github.io/Purchase-Agreement_2/">&lt;p&gt;Purchase Agreement_2&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last updated: June 1, 2018.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PLEASE READ THESE TERMS OF TOKEN SALE CAREFULLY.
IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS OF SALE, DO NOT PURCHASE TOKENS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Risk of Mining Attacks&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As with other decentralised cryptographic tokens based on the Ethereum protocol, the Tokens are susceptible to attacks by miners in the course of validating Token transactions on the Ethereum blockchain, including, but not limited, to double-spend attacks, majority mining power attacks, and selfish-mining attacks. Any successful attacks present a risk to the Tokens, including, but not limited to, accurate execution and recording of transactions involving Tokens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Risk of Hacking and Security Weaknesses&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hackers or other malicious groups or organizations may attempt to interfere with the Tokens in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, malware attacks, denial of service attacks, consensus-based attacks, Sybil attacks, smurfing and spoofing. Furthermore, because it is based on open-source software, there is a risk that a third party or a member of the Company team may intentionally or unintentionally introduce weaknesses into the core infrastructure, which could negatively affect the Tokens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) Risks Associated with Markets for Tokens&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Tokens are intended to be used solely within the Project, and Company will not support or otherwise facilitate any secondary trading or external valuation of Tokens. This restricts the contemplated avenues for using Tokens to the provision or receipt of Services and could therefore create illiquidity risk with respect to the Tokens you hold. Even if secondary trading of Tokens is facilitated by third party exchanges, such exchanges may be relatively new and subject to little or no regulatory oversight, making them more susceptible to fraud or manipulation. Furthermore, to the extent that third parties do ascribe an external exchange value to Tokens (e.g., as denominated in a digital or fiat currency), such value may be extremely volatile and diminish to zero.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6) Risk of Uninsured Losses&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unlike bank accounts or accounts at some other financial institutions, Tokens are uninsured unless you specifically obtain private insurance to insure them. Thus, in the event of loss or loss of utility value, there is no public insurer, such as the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, or private insurance arranged by us, to offer recourse to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7) Risks Associated with Uncertain Regulations and Enforcement Actions&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a risk that in some jurisdictions the CUBE ON tokens and other digital assets might be considered to be a “security”, or other regulated investment now or in the future. Company believes, but does not give representations, warranties or guarantees that tokens are not a security or regulated investment in all jurisdictions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each user of tokens shall bear their own legal or financial consequences of CUBE ON tokens being considered a security or other regulated investment in their respective jurisdiction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every user is required and bound to determine for themselves if the purchase, receipt, trading, use, transfer or disposal of tokens is legal in its jurisdiction, and hereby covenants and agrees not to use CUBE ON tokens should their use not be legal in the relevant jurisdiction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If a user determines that the use of CUBE ON tokens under these Terms is not legal in its jurisdiction, it should not use the CUBE ON tokens, not acquire them and should immediately stop using or possessing them if such case arises.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Acquiring cryptographic tokens for personal possession and exchanging them for other cryptographic tokens will most likely continue to be scrutinized by various regulatory bodies around the world, which has so far given mixed reactions and regulatory impact. The legal ability of Company to provide CUBE ON tokens in some jurisdictions may be eliminated by future regulation or legal actions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the event, it turns out with a high degree certainty that CUBE ON tokens are not legal in certain jurisdiction, Company will either a) cease operations and possible use of CUBE ON tokens in that jurisdiction, or b) adjust CUBE ON tokens in a way to comply with the regulation should that be a possible and viable alternative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8) Risks Arising from Taxation&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tax characterization of Tokens is uncertain. You must seek your own tax advice in connection with purchasing Tokens, which may result in adverse tax consequences to you, including withholding taxes, income taxes and tax reporting requirements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9) Risk of Alternative Networks&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is possible that alternative networks could be established that utilize the same open source code and protocol underlying the Network and attempt to facilitate services that are materially similar to the Services. The Network may compete with these alternative networks, which could negatively impact the Network and Tokens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;10) Risk of Insufficient Interest in the Network or Distributed Applications&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is possible that the Network will not be used by a large number of individuals, companies and other entities or that there will be limited public interest in the creation and development of distributed ecosystems (such as the Network) more generally. Such a lack of use or interest could negatively impact the development of the Network and therefore the potential utility of Tokens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;11) Risks Associated with the Development and Maintenance of the Network&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Network is still under development and may undergo significant changes over time. Although we intend for the Tokens and Network to follow the specifications set forth in White Paper and intend to take commercially reasonable steps toward those ends, we may have to make changes to the specifications of the Tokens or Network for any number of legitimate reasons. This could create the risk that the Tokens, as further developed and maintained, may not meet your expectations at the time of purchase. Furthermore, despite our good faith efforts to develop and maintain, it is still possible that the Network will experience malfunctions or otherwise fail to be adequately developed or maintained, which may negatively impact the Tokens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;12) Risk of an Unfavourable Fluctuation of Ether and Other Currency Value&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Company team intends to use the proceeds from selling Tokens to fund the maintenance and development of the Project. The proceeds of the Token sale will be denominated in Ether or Bitcoin and converted into other cryptographic and fiat currencies. In addition, some pre-sales of the Tokens may also be denominated in fiat currencies. If the value of Ether or other currencies fluctuates unfavourably during or after the Sale Period, the Company team may not be able to fund development or may not be able to develop or maintain the Network in the manner that it intended.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;13) Risk of Dissolution of the Company or Network&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is possible that, due to any number of reasons, including, but not limited to, an unfavourable fluctuation in the value of Ether (or other cryptographic and fiat currencies), decrease in the Tokens’ utility, the failure of commercial relationships, or intellectual property ownership challenges, the Network may no longer be viable to operate, and the Company may dissolve.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;14) Risks Arising from Lack of Governance Rights&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because Tokens confer no governance rights of any kind with respect to the Network or Company or its corporate affiliates, all decisions involving the Network or Company will be made by Company at its sole discretion, including, but not limited to, decisions to discontinue the Network, to create and sell more Tokens for use in the Network, or to sell or liquidate the Company. These decisions could adversely affect the Network and the Tokens you hold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;15) Risks Involving Cloud Storage&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the Company provides a decentralised cloud storage service to individual and institutional clients, including users and applications, the Services are susceptible to a number of risks related to the storage of data in the cloud. While the Company does not have access to the contents of the data stored through the Services, the Services may involve the storage of large amounts of sensitive and/or proprietary information, which may be compromised in the event of a cyberattack or other malicious activity. Similarly, the Services may be interrupted and files may become temporarily unavailable in the event of such an attack or malicious activity. Because users can use a variety of hardware and software that may interface with the Network, there is the risk that the Services may become unavailable or interrupted based on a failure of interoperability or an inability to integrate these third-party systems and devices that the Company does not control with the Company’s Services. The risk that the Services may face increasing interruptions and the Network may face additional security vulnerabilities could adversely affect the Network and therefore the future utility of any Tokens that you hold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;16) Unanticipated Risks&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cryptographic tokens such as the Tokens are a new and untested technology. In addition to the risks included in this article, there are other risks associated with your purchase, holding and use of Tokens, including those that the Company cannot anticipate. Such risks may further materialize as unanticipated variations or combinations of the risks discussed in this article.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Article 5.
ANTI MONEY LAUNDERING-COUNTER TERRORISM FINANCING
5.1. To the extent required by applicable law, the Participant complies with all anti-money laundering and counter-terrorism financing requirements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5.2. The funds, including any fiat, virtual currency or cryptocurrency, the Participant uses to purchase CUBE ON Tokens, are not derived from or related to any unlawful activities, including but not limited to money laundering or terrorist financing, and the Participant will not use the CUBE ON Tokens to finance, engage in, or otherwise support any unlawful activities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Article 6.
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6.1. To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, the Participant disclaims any right or cause of action against the Company of any kind in any jurisdiction that would give rise to any damages whatsoever, on the part of the Company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6.2. The Company shall not be liable to the Participant for any type of damages, whether direct, indirect, incidental, special, punitive, consequential or exemplary (including damages for lost profits, goodwill, use or data), even if and notwithstanding the extent to which the Company has been advised of the possibility of such damages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6.3. The Participant agrees not to seek any refund, compensation or reimbursement from the Company nor related parties, regardless of the reason, and regardless of whether the reason is identified in this Agreement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6.4. In no circumstances will the aggregate joint liability of the Company or related Parties, whether in contract, warrant, tort or other theory, for Damages to the Participant under this Agreement exceed the amount received by the Company from the Participant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6.5. Participant understands and agrees that the Company shall not be liable and disclaims all liability to the Participant in connection with any force majeure, including any industrial disturbances, electrical, telecommunications, hardware, software or other utility failures, software or smart contract bugs or weaknesses, earthquakes, storms, or other nature-related events, blockages, embargoes, riots, acts or orders of government, acts of terrorism or war, technological change, changes in interest rates or other monetary conditions, and, for the avoidance of doubt, changes to any blockchain-related protocol.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Article 7.
DISCLAIMERS&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7.1. To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law and except as otherwise specified in a writing by the Company, the tokens are sold on an “as is” and “as available” basis without warranties of any kind, and the Company expressly disclaim all implied warranties as to the tokens, including, without limitation, implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, title and non-infringement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7.2. The Company does not represent or warrant that the tokens are reliable, current or error-free, meet your requirements, or that defects in the tokens will be corrected and cannot and do not represent or warrant that the tokens or the delivery mechanism for tokens are free of viruses or other harmful components.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7.3. Certain jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion of certain warranties or disclaimer of implied terms in contracts with consumers, so some or all of the exclusions of warranties and disclaimers in this section may not apply to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Article 8.
ARBITRATION&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8.1. Any dispute, controversy or claim arising out of, or in relation to, this agreement, including the validity, invalidity, breach, or termination thereof, shall be resolved by arbitration in accordance with the Rules of International Arbitration in force on the date on which the Notice of Arbitration is submitted in accordance with these Rules.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8.2. The number of arbitrators shall be three. The seat of the arbitration shall be city of Belize. The arbitral proceedings shall be conducted in English language.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8.3. Notice to initiate arbitration proceeding shall be sent by email to the Company at arbitration@bitnation.co. Your notice must include your name, postal address, email address and telephone number, description in reasonable detail of the nature or basis of the Dispute, and the specific relief that you are seeking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Article 9.
GOVERNING LAW AND VENUE&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9.1. These Terms will be governed by and construed and enforced in accordance with the laws of Belize, without regard to conflict of law rules or principles that would cause the application of the laws of any other jurisdiction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9.2. Any Dispute between the Parties arising out or relating to these Terms or its subject matter or formation (including non-contractual Disputes of claims) that is not subject to arbitration will be resolved in the courts of Belize.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SEVERABILITY&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9.3. If any term, clause or provision of these Terms is held unlawful, void or unenforceable, then that term, clause or provision will be severable from these Terms and will not affect the validity or enforceability of any remaining part of that term, clause or provision, or any other term, clause or provision of these Terms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MODIFICATION OF AGREEMENT&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9.4. The Company may modify this Agreement at any time by posting a revised version on the Website, available at https://cubeon.co.in/. The modified terms will become effective upon posting. It is Participant’s responsibility to check the Website regularly for modifications to this Agreement. This Agreement was last modified on the date listed at the beginning of this Agreement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NO PARTNERHIP OF THIRD-PARTY BENEFICIARY.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9.5. Nothing in this Agreement and no action taken by the Parties shall constitute, or be deemed to constitute, a partnership, association, joint venture or other co-operative entity between the Parties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9.6. Nothing in this Agreement and no action taken by the Parties pursuant to this Agreement shall constitute, or be deemed to constitute, either Party the agent of the other Party for any purpose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9.7. No Party has, pursuant to this Agreement, any authority or power to bind or to contract in the name of the other Party. This Agreement does not create any third-party beneficiary rights in any person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATIONS&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9.8. Participant agrees and acknowledges that all agreements, notices, disclosures and other communications that the Company provides the Participant pursuant to this Agreement or in connection with or related to Participant’s purchase of CUBE ON Tokens, including this Agreement may be provided by the Company, in its sole discretion, in electronic form.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/wooriapt.github.io_posts/2018-07-07-Purchase Agreement.md&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://wooriapt.github.io/Purchase-Agreement/&quot; title=&quot;Purchase-Agreement.md&quot;&gt;https://wooriapt.github.io/Purchase-Agreement/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Purchase Agreement_2</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">CUBE ON Token Sale Agreement</title><link href="/wooriapt.github.io/Purchase-Agreement/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="CUBE ON Token Sale Agreement" /><published>2018-07-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-07-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/wooriapt.github.io/Purchase%20Agreement</id><content type="html" xml:base="/wooriapt.github.io/Purchase-Agreement/">&lt;p&gt;Purchase Agreement&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last updated: June 1, 2018.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PLEASE READ THESE TERMS OF TOKEN SALE CAREFULLY. 
IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS OF SALE, DO NOT PURCHASE TOKENS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CUBE ON Token Sale Agreement
This agreement is made by and between This agreement is made by and between Estonia Blockchain Lab number: 
(the Company) and the Participant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Participant and the Company are herein referred collectively as the “Parties”.
If an individual, Participant is at least 18 years old and of sufficient legal age and capacity to purchase CUBE ON tokens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If a legal person, Participant is duly organized, validly existing and in good standing under the laws of its domiciliary jurisdiction 
and each jurisdiction where it conducts business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CUBE ON is developing CUBE ON software, a decentralised jurisdiction for the peer-to-peer creation, arbitration and enforcement of 
agreements, built as an intuitive mobile chat application, as further described in CUBE ON White Paper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By purchasing CUBE ON Tokens from the Company during the Sale Period, you will be bound by these Terms and all terms incorporated 
by reference. If you have any questions regarding these terms, please contact Company at info@cubeon.co.in&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Company and the Participant agree as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Article 1.
BINDING AGREEMENT.
1.1. This Agreement shall be effective and binding on the Parties when Participant clicks the check box on the official 
https://cubeon.co.in website (the “Website”) to indicate that Participant has read, understands and agrees to the term of 
this Agreement or upon Company’s receipt of payment from Participant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WHITE PAPER.
1.2. The Company has prepared the white paper and other materials concerning the sale of CUBE ON Tokens which are available at 
https://cubeon.co.in. The White Paper, as it may be amended from time to time, is hereby incorporated by reference. Participant 
has to read and understands the White Paper and its contents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CUBE ON TOKENS
1.3. The CUBE ON tokens are non-refundable and purchases cannot be cancelled, the Participant may lose all amounts paid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1.4. The CUBE ON tokens do not have any rights, uses, purposes, attributes, functionalities or features, expressed or 
implied, outside the cube ON jurisdiction. Although CUBE ON tokens may be tradable, they are not an investment, currency, 
security, commodity, a swap on a currency or any other kind of financial instrument.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1.5. The purchase of CUBE ON tokens does not provide Participant with rights of any form with respect to the Company or 
its revenues or assets, including, but not limited to any voting, distribution, redemption, liquidation, proprietary 
including all forms of intellectual property, or other financial or legal rights, is not a loan to the Company and does not 
provide Participant with any ownership or other interest in Company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1.6. Purchases and sales of CUBE ON Tokens are not subject to the protections of any governing laws. 
This Agreement and all other documents referred to in this Agreement including the White Paper do not constitute a 
prospectus or offering document, and are not an offer to sell, nor the solicitation of an offer to buy an investment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1.7. Participant acknowledges and understands that the proceeds from the sale of the CUBE ON tokens will be utilized by 
the Company in its sole discretion, as described in the White Paper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Article 2.
CUBE ON TOKEN SALE SPECIFICATIONS
2.1. Important information about the procedures and materials specifications of the Company’s Token sale is provided 
in the White Paper document, including, but not limited to, details regarding the timing and pricing of the Token sale, 
the amount of token for sale, and the Company’s anticipated use of the Token sale proceeds. By purchasing Tokens, 
you acknowledge that you understand and have no objection to these procedure and material specifications. 
Failure to use the official Website and follow such procedures may result in Participant not receiving any CUBE ON Tokens. 
Any Participant of the CUBE ON Tokens sale may lose some or all of the amounts paid in exchange for CUBE ON Tokens, 
regardless of the purchase date. The access or use of the CUBE ON Token and/or the receipt or purchase of CUBE ON token 
through any other means other than the official Website are not sanctioned or agreed to in any way by the Parties. 
Participant should take great care that the website used to purchase CUBE ON Tokens has the following uniform resource locator 
(URL): https://cubeon.co.in/.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NO U.S. PURCHASES.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2.2. The CUBE ON Tokens are not being offered to U.S. person. U.S. person are strictly prohibited and restricted from 
using the CUBE ON Tokens and/or purchasing CUBE ON Tokens and the Company is not soliciting purchases by U.S. 
person or in any way. If a U.S. person purchases CUBE ON Tokens, such person has done so and entered into this Agreement 
on an unlawful, unauthorized and fraudulent basis and this Agreement is null and void.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2.3. The Company is not bound by this Agreement if this Agreement has been entered into by a U.S. person as Participant or 
Participant has entered into this Agreement or has purchased CUBE ON Tokens on behalf of a U.S. 
person, and Company may take all necessary and appropriate actions, in its sole discretion, to invalidate this Agreement, 
including referral of information to the appropriate authorities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2.4. Any U.S. person who uses and/or purchases CUBE ON Tokens or enters into this Agreement on an unlawful, unauthorized or 
fraudulent basis shall be solely liable for, and shall indemnify, defend and hold harmless 
cube ON hps://cubeon.co.in respectively, and past, present and future employees, officers, directors, contractors, consultants, 
equity holders, suppliers, vendors, service providers, parent companies, subsidiaries, affiliates, agents, representatives, 
predecessors, successors and assigns from any damages, losses, liabilities, costs or expenses of any kind, whether direct 
or indirect, consequential, compensatory, incidental, actual, exemplary, punitive or special and including, without limitation, 
any loss of business, revenues, profits, data, use, goodwill or other intangible losses (collectively, the “Damages”) 
incurred by a Party that arises from or is a result of such U.S. person unlawful, unauthorized or fraudulent use of the 
CUBE ON Token Sale Agreement and/or the receipt or purchase of CUBE ON Tokens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CANCELLATION AND REFUSAL OF PURCHASE REQUEST.
2.5. Participant’s purchase of CUBE ON Tokens during the Sale period is final, and there are no refunds or cancellations, 
except as may be required by applicable law or regulation. The Company reserves the right to refuse or cancel Token purchase 
requests at any time in its sole discretion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Article 3.
SECURITY AND DATA PRIVACY
3.1. The Company will implement reasonable and appropriate measures designed to secure access to any device associated with the 
Participant and utilized in connection with the Participant’s purchase of CUBE ON Tokens, private keys to the Participant’s
wallet or account and any other username, password or other login or identifying credentials.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3.2. Upon the Company’s request, the Participant will immediately provide the Company with information and documents that the Company, 
in its sole discretion, deems necessary or appropriate to comply with any laws, regulations, rules or agreements, including without 
limitation judicial process. The Participant acknowledges that the Company may refuse to distribute CUBE ON Tokens to the 
Participant until such requested information is provided.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Article 4.
THE PARTICIPANT KNOWLEDGE OF RISKS
4.1. The Participant has sufficient knowledge and experience in business and financial matters, including a sufficient understanding of blockchain or cryptographic tokens and other digital assets, smart contracts, storage mechanisms ( such as digital or token wallets), blockchain-based software systems and blockchain technology, to be able to evaluate the risks and merits of purchase of CUBE ON tokens and is able to bear the risks thereof, including loss of all amounts paid or loss of CUBE ON tokens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4.2. The Participant has obtained sufficient information in order to make an informed decision to purchase CUBE ON tokens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4.3. By purchasing, holding and using CUBE ON tokens, the Participant expressly acknowledge and assume following risks:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) Risk of losing access to tokens due to loss of Private Keys&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A private key, or a combination of private keys, is necessary to control and dispose of Tokens stored in your digital wallet or vault. Accordingly, loss of requisite private key(s) associated with your digital wallet or vault storing Tokens will result in loss of such Tokens. Moreover, any third party that gains access to such private key(s), including by gaining access to login credentials of a hosted wallet service you use, may be able to misappropriate your Tokens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Risks Associated with the Ethereum Protocol&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because Tokens are based on the Ethereum protocol, any malfunction, breakdown or abandonment of the Ethereum protocol may have a material adverse effect on the Tokens. Moreover, advances in cryptography, or technical advances such as the development of quantum computing, could present risks to the Tokens by rendering ineffective the cryptographic consensus mechanism that underpins the Ethereum protocol.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/wooriapt.github.io/_posts/2018-07-07-Purchase Agreement_2.md&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://wooriapt.github.io/Purchase-Agreement_2/&quot; title=&quot;Purchase Agreement_2.md&quot;&gt;https://wooriapt.github.io/Purchase-Agreement_2/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Purchase Agreement</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Privacy Policy</title><link href="/wooriapt.github.io/Privacy-Policy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Privacy Policy" /><published>2018-07-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-07-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/wooriapt.github.io/Privacy%20Policy</id><content type="html" xml:base="/wooriapt.github.io/Privacy-Policy/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;privacy-policy&quot;&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last updated: March 19, 2018.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WELCOME TO CUBE ON
This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) explains how information about you is collected, used and disclosed by Estonia Blockchain Lab. 
(d/b/a and hereinafter referred to as “CUBE ON”). This Policy applies to cubeon.co.in website. In processing its users’ personal data, CUBE ON complies with this data privacy statement and all applicable statutory provisions, in specific the Data Protection Act 2018.
Collection of Information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We collect information about you in various ways when you use our Services. 
For example, we collect information you provide to us when you register for an account, create a user profile, use our Contact Us form or otherwise communicate with us. Such information may include your name, email address, phone number, biographic information, social media handle, social media profile and/or website URL, picture and any other information you choose to provide. We may also obtain information from other sources and combine that with information we collect on our Services. For example, if you create or log into your account through a third-party social media service, we will have access to certain information from that third-party service, such as your name and account information, in accordance with the authorization procedures determined by such service.
When you access or use our Services, some information is automatically collected. For example, when you visit our Services through your computer, we automatically log your computer’s operating system, Internet Protocol (IP) address and approximate location information derived from your IP address, access times, browser type and language, and the website you visited before navigating to our Services. Additionally, when you visit our Services through your mobile device, we may also collect your unique device ID, device make and model, device IP address, mobile web browser type and version and mobile carrier. We also collect information about your usage and activity on our Services.
COOKIES.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We may automatically collect information using “cookies.” Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive by a website. Among other things, cookies help us improve our Services and your experience. We use cookies to see which areas and features are popular and to count visits to our Services. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove cookies and to reject cookies. If you choose to remove cookies or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or services of our Services.
WEB BEACONS
We may collect information using web beacons (also known as pixel tags). Web beacons are electronic images that may be used on our Services or in our emails. We use web beacons to deliver cookies, count visits, understand usage and campaign effectiveness and to tell if an email has been opened and acted upon.
THIRD PARTY ANALYTICS AND ADVERTISEMENTS
We may also allow third parties to provide analytics services and serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet. These entities may use cookies, web beacons and other devices or technologies to collect information about your use of the Services and other websites and applications, including your IP address, web browser, pages viewed, time spent on pages or in apps, links clicked and conversion information. This information may be used by Cube ON and third parties to, among other things, analyse data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising or other content targeted to your interests and better understand the usage and visitation of our Services and other sites tracked by these third parties.
Use of Information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We may use information about you for various purposes, including to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;•	operate and improve our Services;
•	provide and deliver products and services and send you related information, including confirmations, technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages;
•	respond to your comments and questions and provide customer service;
•	communicate with you about new updates, upcoming events, and other news about services offered by Cube ON and our selected partners;
•	link or combine with other information we obtain from third parties to help understand your needs and provide you with better service;
•	monitor and analyse trends, usage and activities in connection with our Services;
•	personalise and improve the Services and provide advertisements, content or features that match user profiles or interests; and
•	carry out any other purpose for which the information was collected.
Sharing of Information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We may share information about you as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;•	with your consent or at your direction;
•	with third party vendors, consultants and other service providers who are working on our behalf and need access to your information to carry out their work for us;
•	in response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance with any applicable law, regulation or legal process, or as otherwise required by any applicable law, rule or regulation;
•	if we believe your actions are inconsistent with the spirit or language of our user agreements or policies or to protect the rights, property and safety of Cube ON or others; and
•	in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company.
We may also share aggregated or de-identified information that cannot reasonably be used to identify you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Social Sharing Features
The Services may offer social plug-ins (such as the Facebook “Like” button) or other tools or features which let you share actions you take on our Services with other websites, and vice versa. The use of such social sharing features enables the sharing of certain information with your friends or the public, depending on the settings you establish with the third party that provides the feature. For more information about the purpose and scope of data collection and processing in connection with social sharing features, please visit the privacy policies of the third parties that provide these features.
Security
Cube ON takes reasonable measures to help protect information we collect about you in an effort to prevent loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.
Your Information Choices and Changes
Account Information. You may update, correct or delete your account information at any time by logging into your account or emailing us at privacy@CubeON.co.in Please note that we may retain certain information as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may also retain cached or archived copies of your information for a certain period of time.
Promotional Communications. You may opt out of receiving promotional emails from Cube ON by following the instructions in those emails or by modifying your preferences in your account settings. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as emails about your accounts or our ongoing business relations.
Your Privacy Rights. Data Protection Act 2018 governs the collection, use and disclosure of personal data by organisations in a manner that recognises both the right of individuals to protect their personal data and the need of organisations to collect, use or disclose personal data for purposes that a reasonable person would consider appropriate in the circumstances.
Changes to This Policy
Cube ON may change this Policy from time to time. If we make any changes to this Policy, we will notify you by revising the date at the top of the Policy, and in some cases, we may provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to our homepage or sending you an email notification). We encourage you to review this Policy whenever you access the Services to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.
Contact Us&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact us at privacy@cubeon.co.in.
&lt;a href=&quot;http://cubeon.co.in&quot; title=&quot;CUBE ON&quot;&gt;http://cubeon.co.in&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Privacy Policy Last updated: March 19, 2018.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ethereum</title><link href="/wooriapt.github.io/ethCF/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ethereum" /><published>2018-07-06T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-07-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/wooriapt.github.io/ethCF</id><content type="html" xml:base="/wooriapt.github.io/ethCF/">&lt;p&gt;Ethereum
Community
Fund&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blockchains, crypto-assets, and decentralized applications are the most transformative innovations of our generation. 
While poised for substantial growth over the coming years, mainstream adoption remains at an early stage, 
and the appropriate public infrastructure to support billions of users is still a matter of deep R&amp;amp;D.!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://ecf.network./static/media/logo.1b9de7fd.svg&quot; alt=&quot;ECF&quot; width=&quot;60&quot; height=&quot;60&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The aim of the Ethereum Community Fund (ECF) is to provide both funding and connectivity, while shaping the strategic 
direction of the space towards mainstream adoption through the development of infrastructure and compelling 
end-user applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first step towards supporting the growth of the Ethereum ecosystem will be the Infrastructure Grant program. 
This program will be established as a permanent financial endowment to support and aid projects in building crucial 
open-source infrastructure, tooling, and applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://cubeon.co.in&quot; title=&quot;CUBE ON&quot;&gt;http://cubeon.co.in&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Ethereum Community Fund</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">WHAT IS ERC-721</title><link href="/wooriapt.github.io/WHAT-IS-ERC-721/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="WHAT IS ERC-721" /><published>2018-07-06T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-07-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/wooriapt.github.io/WHAT%20IS%20ERC-721</id><content type="html" xml:base="/wooriapt.github.io/WHAT-IS-ERC-721/">&lt;p&gt;WHAT IS ERC-721?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ERC-721 is a free, open standard that describes how to build non-fungible or unique tokens on the Ethereum blockchain. While most tokens are fungible 
(every token is the same as every other token), 
ERC-721 tokens are all unique.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Think of them like rare, one-of-a-kind collectables.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;ERC-20: A CLASS OF IDENTICAL TOKENS.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;ERC-721: A CLASS OF UNIQUE TOKENS&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;###THE STANDARD###&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ERC-721 defines a minimum interface a smart contract must implement to 
allow unique tokens to be managed, owned, and traded. 
It does not mandate a standard for token metadata or restrict adding 
supplemental functions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;    pragma solidity ^0.4.20;

    /// @title ERC-721 Non-Fungible Token Standard
    /// @dev See https://github.com/ethereum/EIPs/blob/master/EIPS/eip-721.md
    ///  Note: the ERC-165 identifier for this interface is 0x80ac58cd
    interface ERC721 /* is ERC165 */ {
        /// @dev This emits when ownership of any NFT changes by any mechanism.
        ///  This event emits when NFTs are created (`from` == 0) and destroyed
        ///  (`to` == 0). Exception: during contract creation, any number of NFTs
        ///  may be created and assigned without emitting Transfer. At the time of
        ///  any transfer, the approved address for that NFT (if any) is reset to none.
        event Transfer(address indexed _from, address indexed _to, uint256 indexed _tokenId);

        /// @dev This emits when the approved address for an NFT is changed or
        ///  reaffirmed. The zero address indicates there is no approved address.
        ///  When a Transfer event emits, this also indicates that the approved
        ///  address for that NFT (if any) is reset to none.
        event Approval(address indexed _owner, address indexed _approved, uint256 indexed _tokenId);

        /// @dev This emits when an operator is enabled or disabled for an owner.
        ///  The operator can manage all NFTs of the owner.
        event ApprovalForAll(address indexed _owner, address indexed _operator, bool _approved);

        /// @notice Count all NFTs assigned to an owner
        /// @dev NFTs assigned to the zero address are considered invalid, and this
        ///  function throws for queries about the zero address.
        /// @param _owner An address for whom to query the balance
        /// @return The number of NFTs owned by `_owner`, possibly zero
        function balanceOf(address _owner) external view returns (uint256);

        /// @notice Find the owner of an NFT
        /// @dev NFTs assigned to zero address are considered invalid, and queries
        ///  about them do throw.
        /// @param _tokenId The identifier for an NFT
        /// @return The address of the owner of the NFT
        function ownerOf(uint256 _tokenId) external view returns (address);

        /// @notice Transfers the ownership of an NFT from one address to another address
        /// @dev Throws unless `msg.sender` is the current owner, an authorized
        ///  operator, or the approved address for this NFT. Throws if `_from` is
        ///  not the current owner. Throws if `_to` is the zero address. Throws if
        ///  `_tokenId` is not a valid NFT. When transfer is complete, this function
        ///  checks if `_to` is a smart contract (code size &amp;gt; 0). If so, it calls
        ///  `onERC721Received` on `_to` and throws if the return value is not
        ///  `bytes4(keccak256(&quot;onERC721Received(address,address,uint256,bytes)&quot;))`.
        /// @param _from The current owner of the NFT
        /// @param _to The new owner
        /// @param _tokenId The NFT to transfer
        /// @param data Additional data with no specified format, sent in call to `_to`
        function safeTransferFrom(address _from, address _to, uint256 _tokenId, bytes data) external payable;

        /// @notice Transfers the ownership of an NFT from one address to another address
        /// @dev This works identically to the other function with an extra data parameter,
        ///  except this function just sets data to &quot;&quot;
        /// @param _from The current owner of the NFT
        /// @param _to The new owner
        /// @param _tokenId The NFT to transfer
        function safeTransferFrom(address _from, address _to, uint256 _tokenId) external payable;

        /// @notice Transfer ownership of an NFT -- THE CALLER IS RESPONSIBLE
        ///  TO CONFIRM THAT `_to` IS CAPABLE OF RECEIVING NFTS OR ELSE
        ///  THEY MAY BE PERMANENTLY LOST
        /// @dev Throws unless `msg.sender` is the current owner, an authorized
        ///  operator, or the approved address for this NFT. Throws if `_from` is
        ///  not the current owner. Throws if `_to` is the zero address. Throws if
        ///  `_tokenId` is not a valid NFT.
        /// @param _from The current owner of the NFT
        /// @param _to The new owner
        /// @param _tokenId The NFT to transfer
        function transferFrom(address _from, address _to, uint256 _tokenId) external payable;

        /// @notice Set or reaffirm the approved address for an NFT
        /// @dev The zero address indicates there is no approved address.
        /// @dev Throws unless `msg.sender` is the current NFT owner, or an authorized
        ///  operator of the current owner.
        /// @param _approved The new approved NFT controller
        /// @param _tokenId The NFT to approve
        function approve(address _approved, uint256 _tokenId) external payable;

        /// @notice Enable or disable approval for a third party (&quot;operator&quot;) to manage
        ///  all of `msg.sender`'s assets.
        /// @dev Emits the ApprovalForAll event. The contract MUST allow
        ///  multiple operators per owner.
        /// @param _operator Address to add to the set of authorized operators.
        /// @param _approved True if the operator is approved, false to revoke approval
        function setApprovalForAll(address _operator, bool _approved) external;

        /// @notice Get the approved address for a single NFT
        /// @dev Throws if `_tokenId` is not a valid NFT
        /// @param _tokenId The NFT to find the approved address for
        /// @return The approved address for this NFT, or the zero address if there is none
        function getApproved(uint256 _tokenId) external view returns (address);

        /// @notice Query if an address is an authorized operator for another address
        /// @param _owner The address that owns the NFTs
        /// @param _operator The address that acts on behalf of the owner
        /// @return True if `_operator` is an approved operator for `_owner`, false otherwise
        function isApprovedForAll(address _owner, address _operator) external view returns (bool);
    }

    interface ERC165 {
        /// @notice Query if a contract implements an interface
        /// @param interfaceID The interface identifier, as specified in ERC-165
        /// @dev Interface identification is specified in ERC-165. This function
        ///  uses less than 30,000 gas.
        /// @return `true` if the contract implements `interfaceID` and
        ///  `interfaceID` is not 0xffffffff, `false` otherwise
        function supportsInterface(bytes4 interfaceID) external view returns (bool);
    }

    interface ERC721TokenReceiver {
        /// @notice Handle the receipt of an NFT
        /// @dev The ERC721 smart contract calls this function on the
        /// recipient after a `transfer`. This function MAY throw to revert and reject the transfer. Return
        /// of other than the magic value MUST result in the transaction being reverted.
        /// @notice The contract address is always the message sender. 
        /// @param _operator The address which called `safeTransferFrom` function
        /// @param _from The address which previously owned the token
        /// @param _tokenId The NFT identifier which is being transferred
        /// @param _data Additional data with no specified format
        /// @return `bytes4(keccak256(&quot;onERC721Received(address,address,uint256,bytes)&quot;))`
        /// unless throwing
        function onERC721Received(address _operator, address _from, uint256 _tokenId, bytes _data) external returns(bytes4);
     }
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ERC-721 started as a EIP draft written by @dete and first came to life in the CryptoKitties project by Axiom Zen&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ERC-721 has since moved out of beta and into a community formalized v1 spec, supported and endorsed by a large number of projects from across the crypto ecosystem. This EIP wouldn’t be possible without time and dedication from a number of community members. Special thanks to @fulldecent and others who have put in tremendous amounts of work to push this forward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://erc721.org&quot; title=&quot;erc721&quot;&gt;http://erc721.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">WHAT IS ERC-721?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">ICO Community Management</title><link href="/wooriapt.github.io/ICO-Community-Management/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="ICO Community Management" /><published>2018-07-06T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-07-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/wooriapt.github.io/ICO%20Community%20Management</id><content type="html" xml:base="/wooriapt.github.io/ICO-Community-Management/">&lt;p&gt;ICO Community Management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ICOs are becoming the new standard for start-ups and business ventures around the world to gain investment by communities. 
Since January 2017, start-ups have raised more than USD1.8 billion through Initial Coin Offerings (ICOs).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blockchain technology entrepreneurs worldwide raised more money through ICO than traditional venture capital investment. 
For most of the tokens, the ICO countdown has already begun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, due to a lack of proper resources, manpower, and legal issues, the preparation of an ICO is a complex project. 
It is important to have the right people on board to plan and launch the ICO campaign to target potential contributors around 
the world – in particular to get numerous big investors rather than a few whales.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/wooriapt.github.io/images/communitymanagement.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is essential to manage the cryptocurrency strategy efficiently because every single person who contacts you on these 
cryptocurrency communities is a potential contributor. 
Due to time zones, channels, language, and range of interest, you might find managing different cryptocurrency communities 
such as telegram group, bitcointalk.org, etc. quite challenging. 
The best way to promote your ICO to the right audience is to hire qualified and experienced ICO community management experts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is a typical ICO community?.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is no universally accepted definition of the cryptocurrency community. 
A group of people who come together in cyberspace to exchange information about cryptocurrency and upcoming ICO is known 
as cryptocurrency community.
Active community engagement is a key part of launching any Initial Coin Offering. 
Medium, bitcointalk, telegram, message boards, social media channels, and other platforms require a constant presence to
build the trust of the community by answering questions promptly as well as correctly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Experienced community management experts provide companies with a team of dexterous and skilled human resources to systematically
optimize the presence of companies and their ICO campaigns on telegram, bitcointalk, and other popular online ICO communities to 
ensure full engagement from the potential investment international community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Telegram.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Telegram is a cloud-based mobile and desktop messaging app with a complete focus on speed and security. 
The “secret chat” of this platform lets the ICO community managing experts have a conversation with end-to-end encryption as well as
other security options. Community managers around the world make use of this platform to exchange information about their ICO campaign
and the client’s company by sending almost any type of file including PDF, Microsoft office, zip, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It offers the possibility for the ICO community manager to pinpoint important message so that new users are always up-to-date. 
Some experts consider it more useful to start a second telegram channel for posting exclusively about the ICO project, team and other
vital information about the company. 
They will always keep the telegram platform clean and clear for the promotion of the ICO campaign to the right audience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bitcointalk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is an online community and forum that systematically allows users around the world to discuss everything related to Bitcoin, ICOs
such as  Seal, Streamity, TokenLend, blockchain, altcoins, and cryptocurrencies. 
The user-friendly forum acts as a perfect way for community members to keep track of the latest news related to Bitcoin and altcoins.
This platform is used by the majority of ICO community managers to promote the ICO campaigns of their clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ICO community managers have chosen to use the Bitcointalk forum to promote and advertise their ICO-related projects via signature
campaigns due to the extremely high level of traffic generated on this forum. 
Community managing experts can go to the service section and apply to one of the offerings, in order to join a signature campaign 
to promote an ICO campaign to the right audience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Experts consider this platform to be an excellent forum for new users to read about the latest developments and options in the
cryptocurrency scene.
Community managers help companies to set up the right kind of account on this forum to promote their ICO campaign to potential
contributors by answering each and every question related to their campaign.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How do community managers help companies with ICO and blockchain related-projects?
It is essential to understand that the majority of ICO community managing experts around the world only take on 
ICO and blockchain-related projects that are legitimate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Leveraging the experience, knowledge, and understanding of the ICO campaigns and blockchain-related projects such as Darico, Bountie,
Ice Rock Mining, the experienced and skilled experts will offer community management services that will maximize potential investment
and strengthen the confidence of potential investors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These experts will also perform quality moderation as well answering questions about the project and token sale of the 
client and you can get a clear idea to know how to invest in ICOs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It will systematically ensure a positive public settlement and strong network effect. 
When the ICO campaign and ICO token sale are over, the community managing services rendered by experts will ensure the long-term 
value of the cryptocurrency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They will help companies to build the trust of the project and token sale with potential investors by answering queries and
questions related to the project on different forums, communities, and platforms.
Positive articles about the team, ICO, and the companies will be posted by the community managing experts on a regular basis on 
various forums, communities, platforms, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Post-ICO support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The community managing team will prepare for the handover at the end of the agreed period of deployment. 
They will recommend suitable contributors to act as responsible authorities to manage the client’s community. 
It will be done for each and every community of the client present on the different channel.
This will ensure that the community of the client will remain committed and healthy for the next growth phase of the
ICO campaign and blockchain-related project. 
In addition to this, many ICO community managers and their team also offer long-term arrangements for managing the community
on different channels, forums, and platforms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How does ICO community management work?.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ICO community managing experts start communication activities about the ICO project as soon as the company decides on doing a 
token sale campaign.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They will create a good user base before the actual launch of the ICO campaign.
They will make use of different types of channel in order to promote the ICO campaign to a much larger audience.
All the queries of the users on different forums and platforms are answered by the community managers to gain the trust of the users around the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They will raise awareness about the project by searching essential articles about the project and posting them on popular 
social media platforms and well-known ICO communities such as telegram and bitcointalk at regular intervals.
Different accounts for different ICO communities will be created by the community managing experts for effective 
promotion and marketing of the clients’ initial coin offering and blockchain-based projects.
Two separate channels on telegram will be formed by the community managers. One group will be precisely created for 
posting about the important and essential announcement information related to ICO, team, Bitcoin, altcoin, or cryptocurrency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many experts believe that forming two channels on the internet of different communities will help companies create great awareness 
about the project within the promised timeframe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Verified and secure accounts are used by the community managing experts while promoting ICO projects.
They will make sure that investors and other members will have clear communication with the clients about bounties or 
any other cryptocurrency token issues.
They will be open to asking for the feedback of users and will systematically adopt ico marketing and promotion strategies 
before bad news or bad press hits their ICO campaign.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They will be open to constructive criticism and work on the marketing campaign to improve the overall changes of converting 
regular users into potential contributors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Challenges faced while promoting and marketing an ICO to the right audience
Dealing with users from different time zones&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Managing community members of different time zones is one of the major challenges faced by community management experts. 
Experts are usually fluent in English and German to effectively communicate with community members.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If a community member is asking questions in any other language, the ICO community management experts will consult another professional
who is fluent in that language to resolve the query successfully.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They will make sure that no questions regarding the clients’ business enterprise and their ICO are left unanswered for too long. 
You can also get more information by attending ICO events which are organized specially for those who plan to launch their 
own ICO project or want to invest in a сrypto-currency tokens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recurring questions&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite having a very informative website in place with all the essential information and their white paper available, most ICO
campaigns suffer from recurring questions related to the duration of the ICO campaign. 
Moreover, the campaign also receives recurring questions related to the general ICO details, start and end date, ico ratings, how to
participate and the supply of tokens after the successful completion of the ICO campaign. 
Some community managing experts build a system where the community members and potential investors are rewarded for the purpose of
spreading and advertising ICO campaign among another community members. 
They will therefore be rewarded for sharing, posting, uploading, joining, and commenting on the ICO campaign.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What benefits do ICOs enjoy if they have good community management?
It is important to act in various ICO community channels and platforms in order to keep the community happy and growing. 
It is not uncommon for there to be no user-driven communication for several hours in the community. 
But a member will not take an ICO or blockchain project seriously if he sees that the last message/comment was a while ago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, community management experts constantly work on different online platforms and search for contribution and articles about the
ICO project. 
They will share these articles and contributions on a regular basis in order to keep the discussion on the community going.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Community managers regularly ask the companies to share all relevant information on anything related to partnerships, 
the team, and the ICO.&lt;br /&gt;
It will help them to actively spread good news about the ICO project with community users. 
Moreover, accurate knowledge about the project will also help them to handle the rumors efficiently and keep the discussion going 
on the channel.
ICO community management professionals and their team will find relevant solutions to each community or channel in case of bad 
news or problems associated with the ICO project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will appear more active in various channels and more credible in comparison with your competitors when skilled professionals 
answer community members queries promptly.
The community managing experts will provide relevant, as well as correct, information to the community members, which will increase 
the chances of these people deciding best ICOs to invest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Leveraging their vast experience of managing ICOs like Global Spy,  BunnyToken, PumaPay, and many more on different channels,
they will spend a lot of time dealing with all the questions that arise on prominent ICO channels as quickly and correctly 
as possible. 
The digital world is extremely fast-moving, so it is essential for the experts to ensure that they resolve issues and questions 
of the community members at a reasonable pace. 
If answering the community members’ questions about the ICO takes too long, potential contributors will lose interest quickly. 
You can also view ICO planning guide from our website which helps you to implement the perfect and systematic strategy for 
investing in ICOs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is essential that the community manager is organized and has in-depth knowledge and understanding of the features 
of the various community channels. 
They should know how to promote and grow an ICO to a particular community channel. 
They should also have proper knowledge about the channel such as how to send personal messages, block people, pinned messages, and
spamming, etc. 
in order to promote the ICO to the right kind of audience by answering genuine questions audience correctly and within a few minutes. 
In the same ways, Influencer marketing is a powerful route to market for ICO, where famous brand campaigns reach engaged audiences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Assist companies to choose the right channel
ICO community managers will assist the company to choose different communities and channels in order to promote the ICO projects to the
right audience. 
The channels and respective community are maintained by the ICO community manager. 
In order to access as many people as possible, the community management team do not use a single community but find a good mix of communities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/wooriapt.github.io/images/github.png&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;github&quot;&gt;Github.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Twitter, telegram, bitcointalk, etc. are some of the important channels that ICO community managers use to communicate 
directly with the community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://cubeon.co.in&quot; title=&quot;CUBE ON&quot;&gt;http://cubeon.co.in&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">ICO Community Management.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">name coin view</title><link href="/wooriapt.github.io/name-coin/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="name coin view" /><published>2018-07-05T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-07-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/wooriapt.github.io/name%20coin</id><content type="html" xml:base="/wooriapt.github.io/name-coin/">&lt;p&gt;Namecoin
Namecoin is an experimental open-source technology which improves decentralization, security, censorship resistance, privacy, and speed of certain components of the Internet infrastructure such as DNS and identities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(For the technically minded, Namecoin is a key/value pair registration and transfer system based on the Bitcoin technology.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin frees money – Namecoin frees DNS, identities, and other technologies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What can Namecoin be used for?
Protect free-speech rights online by making the web more resistant to censorship.
Attach identity information such as GPG and OTR keys and email, Bitcoin, and Bitmessage addresses to an identity of your choice.
Human-meaningful Tor .onion domains.
Decentralized TLS (HTTPS) certificate validation, backed by blockchain consensus.
Access websites using the .bit top-level domain.
Proposed ideas such as file signatures, voting, bonds/stocks/shares, web of trust, notary services, and proof of existence. (To be implemented.)
What does Namecoin do under the hood?
Securely record and transfer arbitrary names (keys).
Attach a value (data) to the names (up to 520 bytes).
Transact the digital currency namecoins (NMC).
Like bitcoins, Namecoin names are difficult to censor or seize.
Lookups do not generate network traffic (improves privacy).
Namecoin was the first fork of Bitcoin and still is one of the most innovative “altcoins”. It was first to implement merged mining and a decentralized DNS. Namecoin was also the first solution to Zooko’s Triangle, the long-standing problem of producing a naming system that is simultaneously secure, decentralized, and human-meaningful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More Information
Namecoin Identities
.bit DNS
News
2018-07-01 Namecoin’s merged mining, which allows miners to simultaneously mine a parent chain (usually Bitcoin) and any number of child chains (e.g. Namecoin and Huntercoin), is made possible by AuxPoW (auxilliary proof of work). AuxPoW is a clever trick (first proposed by Bitcoin founder Satoshi Nakamoto, and first implemented by Namecoin founder Vincent Durham) that allows a block in the parent chain to commit to a block in any number of child chains, such that the child block can reference the parent block’s PoW and thereby prove that the PoW committed to both the parent and child block. AuxPoW doesn’t impose any changes for the parent chain’s consensus rules, but it does constitute a hardfork for the child chain (even for lightweight SPV clients of the child chain). As a result, making Electrum-NMC validate PoW properly requires patching Electrum to support AuxPoW.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read more…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2018-06-07 We’ve released Electrum-NMC v3.1.3-beta1. This release supports Namecoin currency transactions, but does not yet support AuxPoW or name transactions. This release is based on work by both ahmedbodi and myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read more…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2018-05-28 Last year, Ahmed posted about his progress porting Electrum to Namecoin. Electrum-NMC has been on the back burner for me lately, due to the TLS and BitcoinJ efforts taking up most of my time. However, today I found time to inspect Ahmed’s branch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read more…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2018-05-21 Last episode: When we last left our hero, tlsrestrict_nss_tool had a few unfixed bugs that made it unusable on Windows. Everyone believed those bugs would be the final ones. Were they? And now, the conclusion to our 2-part special:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read more…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2018-05-20 Now that we got NSS certutil reproducibly cross-compiled for Windows, initial testing has begun on tlsrestrict_nss_tool for Windows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read more…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2018-05-17 In a previous post where I introduced tlsrestrict_nss_tool, I mentioned that NSS’s certutil doesn’t have official binaries for Windows, and that “At some point, we’ll probably need to start cross-compiling NSS ourselves, although I admit I’m not sure I’m going to enjoy that.” Well, we’ve reached that point, and it was an interesting adventure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read more…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2018-05-14 I discussed in a previous post some experimental work on making ncdumpzone output a Firefox certificate override list. At that time, the procedure wasn’t exactly user-friendly: you’d need to run ncdumpzone from a terminal, redirect the output to a file, close Firefox, delete whatever existing .bit entries existed in the existing Firefox certificate override file, append the ncdumpzone output to that file, and relaunch Firefox. I’ve now integrated some code into ncdns that can automate this procedure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read more…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2018-05-12 One of the more obscure DNS record types is DNAME (AKA the Namecoin “translate” JSON field), which is basically a DNS redirect for an entire subtree. For example, currently radio.bit. has a DNAME record pointing to biteater.dtdns.net., which means that any subdomain (e.g. batman.radio.bit.) becomes a CNAME redirect (e.g. to batman.biteater.dtdns.net.).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read more…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2018-04-19 We’ve released cross_sign_name_constraint_tool v0.0.2 and tlsrestrict_nss_tool v0.0.2. These implement the functionality described in my previous post on Integrating Cross-Signing with Name Constraints into NSS (and the earlier posts that that post links to).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read more…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2018-04-17 We’ve released ncdns v0.0.6. List of changes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read more…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earlier news&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the latest news go to the Namecoin forum or check out r/namecoin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Official anouncements will also be made on this BitcoinTalk thread.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Donate
Help keep us strong. You can donate to the Namecoin project here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Participate
With Namecoin you can make a difference. We need your help to free information, especially in documentation, marketing, and coding. You are welcome at the forum. There may be bounties, too.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Namecoin Namecoin is an experimental open-source technology which improves decentralization, security, censorship resistance, privacy, and speed of certain components of the Internet infrastructure such as DNS and identities.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Today’s question!?</title><link href="/wooriapt.github.io/Today's-question/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Today's question!?" /><published>2018-07-05T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-07-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/wooriapt.github.io/Today's%20question</id><content type="html" xml:base="/wooriapt.github.io/Today's-question/">&lt;p&gt;“Today’s question.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q1. Lite Paper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q2. Token Structure and Design.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1.ICO period : Start time &amp;amp; Ending Time.      &lt;br /&gt;
2.Coin quantity to be issued.     &lt;br /&gt;
3.1coin expected price.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q3. Ethereum Quantity of distribution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q4. ICO period Gas Fee total.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/wooriapt.github.io/images/20170803ddbfe1589fd39a3f9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">“Today’s question.”</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Terms of Use of Website</title><link href="/wooriapt.github.io/Terms-of-Use-of-Website/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Terms of Use of Website" /><published>2018-07-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-07-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/wooriapt.github.io/Terms%20of%20Use%20of%20Website</id><content type="html" xml:base="/wooriapt.github.io/Terms-of-Use-of-Website/">&lt;p&gt;Terms of Use of Website (“TERMS”).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;last-updated-march-19-2018&quot;&gt;Last updated: March 19, 2018.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PLEASE THEREFORE READ THESE TERMS CAREFULLY EACH TIME YOU USE THIS WEBSITE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This website is owned and operated by Estonia Blockchain Lab. Belize (hereinafter “cube ON”). CUBE ON has the sole discretion to change any Term at any time.
By accessing or using this website, you unconditionally accept these Terms. If you do not agree to be bound by any Term, please do not access or use this website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Restriction on Use of Materials.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No material including without limitation, the website design and layout, graphics, images and hyperlinks from this website may be imitated, modified, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted or distributed in any way, without the prior written permission of CUBE ON.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You must not do any act that will or may interfere with this website’s accessibility and/or proper functioning, or that will or may place an unreasonable or disproportionately large load on CUBE ON’s servers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unauthorized modification and/or interference, misuse, abuse or unauthorized use of this website and any of its materials may violate CUBE ON’s and/or third party owners’ intellectual property rights, and may also be an offence under the Data Protection Act 2018.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We may make (but are not obligated to make) the source code for the softwarewe develop available for download as open source software. You agree to be boundby, and comply with, any license agreement that applies to this open source software.You will not indicate that you are associated with us in connection with your use,modifications or distributions of this open source software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we host any software and enable you to access and use such software throughour websites including this Website, then these terms will apply to such accessand use, as well as any license agreements that we may enter into with you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer of Warranties and Liability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This website has been compiled in good faith by CUBE ON.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IMPORTANT: THIS WEBSITE AND ITS MATERIALS ARE PROVIDED “AS IS” AND WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMISSIBLE AND SUBJECT AND PURSUANT TO APPLICABLE LAW, CUBE ON DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, ANY WARRANTIES AS TO FUNCTIONALITY, OPERABILITY, ACCESSIBILITY, ACCURACY, CORRECTNESS, RELIABILITY, UPDATEDNESS, TIMELINESS, SATISFACTORY QUALITY, MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. CS DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE WEBSITE, ITS MATERIALS AND FUNCTIONS CONTAINED IN THE MATERIALS WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE, OR THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED OR THAT THIS WEBSITE AND THIS SERVER THAT MAKES IT AVAILABLE ARE FREE OF ANY COMPUTER VIRUS AND/OR OTHER HARMFUL OR CORRUPTING CODE, PROGRAMME, MACRO AND SUCH LIKE ELEMENTS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;limitation-of-liability&quot;&gt;Limitation of Liability.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Subject to applicable law, under no circumstances, including, but not limited to negligence, shall CUBE ON be liable for any direct or indirect damages howsoever caused to any person that result from any person’s use, misuse, abuse, access of, or inability to access or use the website and/or its materials.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Changes &amp;amp; Access.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any change may be made to the website and any of its materials from time to time at CUBE ON’s sole discretion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CUBE ON reserves the right to deny access to this website to any particular person or access from any particular internet address to this website, at any time, without having to provide its reasons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Suggestions, Comments and Feedback.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any communications you send to this website or otherwise to CUBE ON by electronic mail are on a non-confidential basis, and CUBE ON is under no obligation to refrain from reproducing, publishing or otherwise using them in any way for any purpose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CUBE ON shall be free to use the content of any such communications, including any ideas, inventions, concepts, techniques or know-how disclosed herein, for any purpose, including the developing, manufacturing and/or marketing of goods or services. Further, CUBE ON shall be free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how or techniques contained in such information for any purpose whatsoever including but not limited to developing and marketing services incorporating such information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;hyperlinks&quot;&gt;Hyperlinks.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This website contains links to other websites which are not maintained by CUBE ON. Similarly, other websites may contain links to this website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CUBE ON is not responsible for the contents of those websites and shall not be liable for any damages or injury arising from the contents of those websites. Any links to other websites are provided as a convenience to you as a user of this website and does not imply CUBE ON’s endorsement of the linked websites or association with their operators. CUBE ON disclaims all responsibility and liability for the use of linked websites, which are accessed and used at user’s own risk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any third party that wishes to establish links to this website should notify CUBE ON of their intention prior to doing so. CUBE ON reserves the right to deny permission for any such links to this website. If, however CUBE ON gives its permission for any such links, CUBE ON is not under any obligation to establish reciprocal links with the third party.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;governing-law&quot;&gt;Governing Law.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The access and use of this website and its materials, and the Terms shall be governed by the domestic laws of the Belize.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right of Access
CUBE ON reserves all rights to deny or restrict access to this site by any particular person, or to block access from a particular internet address to this site at any time, without ascribing any reasons whatsoever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Acceptable Use Policy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You must only use the content or services provided through this Website for their stated purpose. You must not use this Website to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;a. publish, post, send, upload, submit, display or disseminate any information or material and/or otherwise make available or engage in any conduct that is unlawful, discriminatory, harassing, libellous, defamatory, abusive, threatening, harmful, offensive, obscene, tortious or otherwise objectionable; b. display, upload or transmit material that encourages conduct that may constitute a criminal offence, result in civil liability or otherwise violate or breach any applicable laws, regulations or code of practice; c. interfere or violate the legal rights (such as rights of privacy and publicity) of others or violate others use or enjoyment of this Website; d. violate any applicable laws or regulations; e. use this Website or links on this Website in any manner that could interfere with, disrupt, negatively affect or inhibit other users from using this Website or links on this Website or that could damage, disable, overburden or impair the functioning of this Website or our servers or any networks connected to any of our servers in any manner; f. create a false identity for the purpose of misleading others or fraudulently or otherwise misrepresent yourself to be another person or a representative of another entity including, but not limited to, an authorized user of this Website or a block.one representative, or fraudulently or otherwise misrepresent that you have an affiliation with a person, entity or group; g. mislead or deceive us, our representatives and any third parties who may rely on the information provided by you, by providing inaccurate or false information, which includes omissions of information; h. disguise the origin of any material transmitted through the services provided by this Website (whether by forging message/packet headers or otherwise manipulating normal identification information); i. violate, infringe or misappropriate any intellectual or industrial property right of any person (such as copyright, trademarks, patents, or trade secrets, or other proprietary rights of any party) or commit a tort; j. upload files that contain viruses, Trojan horses, worms, time bombs, cancelbots, corrupted files, or any other similar software or programs that may damage the operation of another’s computer or property; k. send, upload, display or disseminate or otherwise make available material containing or associated with spam, junk mail, advertising for pyramid schemes, chain letters, virus warnings (without first confirming the authenticity of the warning), or any other form of unauthorised advertising or promotional material; l. access any content, area or functionality of this Website that you are prohibited or restricted from accessing or attempt to bypass or circumvent measures employed to prevent or limit your access to any content, area or functionality of this Website; m. obtain unauthorized access to or interfere with the performance of the servers which host this Website or provide the services on this Website or any servers on any associated networks or otherwise fail to comply with any policies or procedures relating to the use of those servers; n. attempt to gain unauthorized access to any services or products, other accounts, computer systems, or networks connected to any of our servers through hacking, password mining, or any other means; o. obtain or attempt to obtain any materials or information through any means not intentionally made available through this Website or its services; p. harvest or otherwise collect, whether aggregated or otherwise, data about others including e-mail addresses and/or distribute or sell such data in any manner; q. use any part of this Website other than for its intended purpose; or r. 
use this Website to engage in or promote any activity that violates these terms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ownership and Copying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This site, including all content uploaded by users, is owned and operated by CUBE ON. Unless otherwise stated, all contents of this site should not be reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, modified, transmitted or distributed in any way, without the prior written permission of CUBE ON, whichever is applicable. Doing so constitutes a violation of our copyright and intellectual property rights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All contents posted express the views of only the author. CUBE ON will not be held liable or responsible for any content posted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Agreeemnt to Our Terms of Use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By uploading and posting any material on this site, you indicate to CUBE ON that you have read and agreed to our terms and conditions. These Terms of Use may be changed from time to time. Changes will be posted on this page and your use of this Site after such changes have been posted will constitute your agreement to the modified Terms of Use and all of the changes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://cubeon.co.in&quot; title=&quot;CUBE ON&quot;&gt;http://cubeon.co.in&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Terms of Use of Website (“TERMS”).</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">CUBE ON Token..?</title><link href="/wooriapt.github.io/CUBE-ON-Token/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="CUBE ON Token..?" /><published>2016-07-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2016-07-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/wooriapt.github.io/CUBE%20ON%20Token</id><content type="html" xml:base="/wooriapt.github.io/CUBE-ON-Token/">&lt;p&gt;CUBE ON Arbitration and Utility Token (XCB)..?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The CUBE ON Arbitration and Utility Token (XCB) is an ERC20 compatible in-app token for the CUBE ON Jurisdiction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The XCB token rewards good reputation and is issued on CUBE ON when Citizens accumulate non-tradable reputation tokens 
through creating a contract, successfully completing a contract or resolving a dispute attached to a contract.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;XCB is an algorithmic reputation token, an arbitration currency based on performance rather than purchasing power, 
popularity or attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The distribution mechanism for XCB tokens on CUBE ON is an autonomous agent, Lucy, which will initially 
launch on Ethereum as a smart contract.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This mechanism is blockchain agnostic and can be ported to any viable smart contract platform.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="[&quot;issues&quot;]" /><summary type="html">CUBE ON Arbitration and Utility Token (XCB)..?</summary></entry></feed>